Guide to the Kenneth C.M. Sills: Administrative Records A01.02.08
George J. Mitchell Department of Special Collections & Archives, Bowdoin College Library, Brunswick, Maine 04011
- World War II Correspondence, 1940-1946, A01.02.08.13; 5.0 linear feet
  - Burton, Robert S. (Bow 1943) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Bush, Walter M. (Bow 1940) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Butler, F. Coit (Bow 1944) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Butler, Roland E. (Bow 1925) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Byron, Walter F. (Bow 1945) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Callahan, Daniel H. (Bow 1943) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Callman, I. B. (Bow 1944) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Campbell, Beverly (Bow 1946) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Campbell, Philip S. (Bow 1939) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Campbell, Wallace J. (Bow 1945) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Canavello, Frederick (Bow ch 1940) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Carey, Joseph F. (Bow 1944) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Carmichael, Douglass (Bow 1944) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Carr, Winthrop W. (1943) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Carrigan, Peter P. (Bow 1942) (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Carter, George (Bow 1935) (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Carter, W. Hodding (Bow 1927) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Cartland, John E. Jr. (Bow 1939) (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Cass, M. W. (Bow 1937) (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Cay, Donald F. (Bow 1943) (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Chamberland, Malcolm (Bow 1946) (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Chandler, Robert E. (Bow 1941) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Chapen, John (Bow 1941) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Chapman, H. Philip Jr. (Bow 1930) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Chapman, Philip F. Jr. (1938 Bow) (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Chase, Charles W. (Bow 1932) (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Cheetham, William H. (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Chisholm, George E. (Bow 1936) (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Chism, Murray F. (Bow 1942) (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Cing-Mars, Robert J. (Bow 1943) (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Claff, Leslie A. (Bow 1926) (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Clark, Freeman D. (Bow 1938) (Box 2, Folder 50a)
  - Clark, Harry B. (Bow 1936) (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Clark, Robert S. (Bow 1929) (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Clark, Thomas D. (Bow 1926) (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Clarke, Clinton B. (Bow 1946) (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Clarke, Raymond M. (Bow 1947) (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Cleaves, Fort B. (Bow 1932) (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Cleaves, George M. (Bow 1934) (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Cleaves, Robert A. (Bow 1935) (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Clenott, William (Bow 1946) (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Clive, Frederick T. (Bow 1945) (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Clogston, R. Benjamin (Bow 1933) (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Cobb, Richard W. (Bow 1922) (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Coburn, John W. (Bow 1919) (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Coffin, Robert P. T. Jr. (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Cohen, Leonard (Bow 1939) (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Coit, Charles A. (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Cole, Charles W. (Bow n 1927) (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Cole, Philip (Bow 1912) (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Cole, Philip Jr. (Bow ch 1943) (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Cole, Taylor (Bow 1945) (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Colton, Robert E. (Bow 1944) (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Conant, Donald B. (Bow 1941) (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Congdon, John (Bow 1943) (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Connor, Brian (Bow 1927) (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Coombs, Robert W. (Bow 1940) (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Cooper, Edward W. (Bow 1941) (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Cooper, Thomas A. (Bow 1944) (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Cormack, Warren E. (Bow 1946) (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Cowan, Casper F. (Bow 1936) (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Cowley, Wilbur (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Craig, John H. (Bow 1941) (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Crain, Charles M. (Bow 1946) (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Crowen, John V. (Bow 1943) (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Crawford, A. Chandler (Bow 1937) (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Creighton, John (Bow 1942) (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Cressey, Stanley B. (Bow 1940) (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Cronin, Joseph S. (Bow 1943) (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Cronkhite, Leonard W. (Bow 1941) (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Cross, Harold L. (Bow 1937) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Cross, Robert (Bow 1945) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Crossman, Mortimer B. (Bow 1920) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Crowell, James D. (Bow 1935) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Curry, John J. (Bow 1946) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Curtis, Charles W. (Bow 1947) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Curtis, John A. (Bow 1945) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dana, Edward F. (Bow 1929) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dana, Lawrence (Bow 1935) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dane, Francis S. Jr. (Bow 1931) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Davidson, George T. (Bow 1938) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Davidson, Paul L. (Bow ch 1945) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Davis, Evan G. (Bow 1938) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Davis, Frank R. (Bow 1941) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Davis, Hubert V. (Bow 1923) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Davis, M. Ben (Bow 1926) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Davis, Nicholas (Bow ch 1946) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Richard H. (Bow 1934) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Davis, Stuart K. (Bow 1935) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Davis, William H. (Bow 1939) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Davis, William M. (Bow 1949) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Davison, Howard A. (Bow 1930) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Dawson, George R. (Bow 1945) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Dean, William H. (1930) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Dell, Russell C. (Bow 1936) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Demarest, Lawrence M. (Bow 1945) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Denham, Enos M. (Bow 1939) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Denison, Orville B. (Bow 1941) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Denismore, M. A. (Bow 1946) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - de Sherbmin, Robert I. (Bow 1945) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Devine, Donald T. (Bow 1943) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Dick, John A. (Bow 1945) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Dickson, David (Bow 1941) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Dolan, Henry A. (Bow 1949) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Dolan, James D. (Bow 1943) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Donahue, Walter S. (Bow 1944) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Donaldson, John (Bow 1944) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Donavan, Peter (Bow 1940) (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Donovan, Timothy (Bow 1948) (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Donworth, John S. (Bow 1931) (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Doubleday, James A. (Bow 1941) (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Dougherty, William A. (Bow 1946) (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Douglas, Paul H. (Bow 1913) (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Downs, Thomas L. (Bow 1927) (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Doyle, Elliot L. (Bow 1928) (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Doyle, Richard (Bow 1940) (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Drake, B. W. (Bow 1945) (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Draper, James B. (Bow 1949) (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Driscoll, Francis J. (Bow 1942) (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Dufton, George F. (Bow 1930) (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Duggan, Norman E. (Bow 1944) (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Dunbar, George A. (Bow 1939) (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Dunbar, Roger D. (Bow 1941) (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Dunlap, Edward A. III (Bow 1940) (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Dunn, Leo J. (Bow 1947) (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Durant, E. T. (Bow 1928) (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Dwelley, H. R. (Bow 1949) (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Dyer, J. Donald (Bow 1937)? (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Dyment, Harold E. (Bow 1940) (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Eames, Paul H. Jr. (Bow 1946) (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Early, James (Bow 1945) (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Eastman, R. Kimball Jr. (Bow 1944)? (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Eaton, Franklin (Bow 1942) (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Eaton, Maxwell A. (Bow 1937) (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Eck, Arnold R. (Bow 1942) (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Ecke, Robert S. (Bow 1931) (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Eckfeldt, Roger W. (Bow 1943) (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Eddy, Warren Jr. (Bow 1943) (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Edwards, Alfred B. (Bow 1932) (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Edwards, Charles P. (Bow 1941) (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Edwards, Robert L. (Bow 1943) (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Edwards, Roger (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Eklund, Wilhelm C. (Bow 1941) (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Eliot, William L. (Bow 1944) (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Elliot, R. Bruce (Bow 1945) (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Elliot, W. N. (Bow 1943) (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Elliott, C. James (Bow ch 1941) (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Elliott, Gilbert M. Jr. (Bow 1925) (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Ellis, Robert W. (Bow 1941) (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Evans, John C. (Bow 1941) (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Eveleth, Richard T. (Bow 1941) (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Evens, Delos W. (Bow 1932) (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Everett, Edward F. (Bow 1940) (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Evers, Wallace K. (Bow 1946) (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Falconer, Robert C. (Bow 1937) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Farley, Charles H. (Bow 1930) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Farr, Henry L. (Bow 1929) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Farrington, Hugh F. (Bow ch 1944) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fay, John G. (Bow 1934) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fearon, Harold R. (Bow 1936) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ferris, Alden C. (Bow 1939) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Field, R. C. (Bow 1946) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Finnagan, Waller P. (Bow 1945) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fish, William H. (Bow 1943) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fisher, Stanwood E. Jr. (Bow 1941) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Fitts, David W. (Bow 1938) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Flanagan, J. V. (Bow 1946) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Flint, Putnam P. (Bow 1942) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Flint, Vasmer L. (Bow 1938) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Flynt, William F. (Bow 1944) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Fogg, George E. Jr. (Bow 1943) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Fogg, Sanford L. Jr. (Bow 1927) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Foran, John (Bow 1946) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Forbes, John R. (Bow 1938) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Fortin, Christian (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Foster, Robert J. (Bow 1925) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Foster, Robert M. (1934) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Fox, Robert B. (Bow 1938) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Frazier, Claude R. (Bow 1938) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Freeman, James C. (Bow 1934) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Freese, John B. (Bow 1918) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Freme, Ferris A. (Bow 1942) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Friedmann, John R. P. (Bow 1947) (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Frost, Stevens L. (Bow 1942) (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Fry, William F. (Bow 1946) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Frye, John H. (Bow 1938) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Gammon, Alan L. (Bow 1943) (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Gardner, Richard F. (Bow 1942) (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Garvey, Edward C. (Bow 1945) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Gates, Ellis L. (Bow 1937) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Gates, Philip B. (Bow 1940) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Gatterer (Gordon), Herbert G. (Bow 1940) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Gauvreau, Norman O. (Bow 1943) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Gentry, Newell E. (Bow 1940) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Gillett, Newell E. (Bow 1940) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Gilman, Elvin J. (Bow 1940) (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Gilpatrick, Paul H. (Bow 1937) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Gingras, Richard C. (Bow 1944) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Girard, Wilfred H. (Bow 1939) (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Golden, Balfour H. (Bow 1944) (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Golderman, Robert W. (Bow 1947) (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Goldman, Jack D. (Bow 1937) (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Gordon, Herbert G. (Bow 1940) (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Gordon, Robert G. (Bow 1941) (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Goudouros, James T. (Bow 1946) (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Gould, Albert P. (Bow 1937) (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Gray, Deane B. (Bow 1942) (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Gray, Eldon (Bow 1926) (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Greene, Horace S. (Bow 1939) (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Greene, William M. (Bow ch 1946) (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Greenly, J. A. (Bow 1945) (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Gregory, Alfred L. (Bow 1943) (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Griffith, George M. (Bow 1937) (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Griffith, Joseph H. (Bow 1940) (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Guy, Basil J. (Bow 1947) (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Gwynn, Frederick L. (Bow 1937) (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Hackwell, R. Lloyd (Bow 1934) (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Haldane, Andrew A. (Bow 1941) (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Hale, Richard F. (Bow ch 1944) (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Hales, James A. (Bow 1940) (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Haley, Bruce T. (Bow 1941) (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Hall, W. Bradford (Bow 1941) (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Hall, Crowell T. (Bow 1937) (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Hall, Frederick W. (Bow 1942) (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Hall, James B. (Bow 1947) (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Hall, Peter A. (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Hall, W. B. (Bow 1941) (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Hamblen, Arthur (Bow 1948) (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Hanscom, Ward T. (Bow 1941) (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Hanson, Arthur W. (Bow 1941) (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Hanson, Richard C. (Bow 1942) (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Happ, William (Bow 1946) (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Harding, R. R. (Bow 1941) (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Harkness, Robert (Bow 1926) (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Harrington, Robert W. (Bow 1934) (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Hartshorn, Charles (Bow 1941) (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Hastings, Merrill G. (Bow ch 1914) (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Hatch, Lloyd H. (Bow 1940) (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Hathaway, Alton H. (Bow 1933) (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Hauserman, Frank B. (Bow 1945) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hawkins, William S. (Bow 1938) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hawke, Edward A. (Bow 1946) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Hayes, Paul T. (Bow 1931) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hayward, Ralph C. (Bow 1943) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Heflin, Robert D. (Bow 1943) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Hellman, Alan G. (Bow ch 1944) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Henderson, C. F. C. (Bow 1937) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hendrickson, Harold M. (Bow 1942) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Hermann, Paul H. (Bow 1940) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Herrick, James E. (Bow 1945) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Herron, Philip W. (Bow 1946) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Hersey, Francis C. (Bow 1946) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Hess, John E. (Bow 1944) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Heussler, John M. (Bow 1946) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Heymann, Alfred L. (Bow 1945) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Heymann, Melvin (Bow 1948) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Heywood, George H. (Bow 1943) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Hickox, John B. (Bow 1934) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Higgins, J. R. (Bow 1943) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Hill, Calvin A. (Bow 1940) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hill, Robert B. (Bow 1942) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Hills, Leonard (Bow 1943) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Hinkley, Walter (Bow 1934) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Hirch, Leonard W. (Bow 1947) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Holden, Dudley F. (Bow 1938) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Holmes, Alonzo B. (Bow 1921) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Holmes, Clyde B. (Bow 1940) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Holtman, Frank G. (Bow 1947) (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Holway, William G. (Bow 1926) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Hopkins, John S. (Bow 1927) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Hormell, Robert S. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Houghton, Charles F. (Bow 1915) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Howard, Edward R. (Bow ch 1941) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Howard, Henry M. (Bow 1918) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Howard, Marshall H. A. (Bow ch 1945) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Howard, Thomas W. (Bow 1939) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Hudon, Edward G. (Bow 1937), and Louis J. (Bow 1938) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Hughes, Albert (Bow 1939) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Hunt, Emerson W. (Bow 1923) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Hunt, Enoch W. (Bow 1934) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Hunt, Mansfield L. (Bow 1937) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Hunter, James B. (Bow 1939) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Hupper, John R. (Bow 1950) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Hussey, Stetson H. Jr. (Bow 1941) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Hutchings, George W. (Bow 1943) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Hutchinson, Melville C. (Bow 1939) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Hyde, Richard W. (Bow 1943) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Ingalls, Roscoe C. (Bow 1943) (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Ireland, Charles T. (Bow 1942) (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Irish, James T. Jr. (Bow 1945) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - "Jack" (?) (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Jack, Paul E. (Bow 1933) (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Jackson, Henry B. (Bow 1936) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - James, David A. (Bow 1943) (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Janney, Raymond Barton (Bow 1942) (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Jenkisson, John F. (Bow 1941) (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Johnson, Joseph H. (Bow 1944) (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Johnson, Philip M. (Bow 1940) (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Johnson, Robert L. (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Johnston, David B. (Bow 1945) (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Johnston, R. C. (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Johnstone, Richard C. (Bow 1944) (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Jones, F. P. (Bow 1946) (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Joy, Ernest H. (Bow 1925) (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Joy, Franklin L. (Bow 1944) (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Jurgenson, Robert G. (Bow 1945) (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Kahill, Charles F. (Bow 1934) (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Kane, Howard F. (Bow 1909) (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Kane, James A. (Bow 1941) (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Karsokas, B. H. (Bow 1939) (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Keefe, Thaddeus K. (Bow 1941) (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Keene, B. E. (Bow 1947) (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Kelley, Forbes W. (Bow 1941) (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Kelly, John J. (Bow 1935) (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Kendruck, Albert S. (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Kennedy, Robert M. (Bow 1942) (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Keniston, Allan G. (Bow 1944) (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Kent, George G. (Bow 1947) (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Keylor, Arthur W. (Bow 1942) (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Kidd, Ralph E. (Bow 1943) (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Kileski, Frederick G. (Bow 1920) (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Kimball, J. Frank (Bow 1947) (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Kinnard J. R. (Bow 1941) (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Kinsey, Charles (Bow 1940) (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Kinsley, Samuel E. (Bow 1946) (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Kitfield, David B. (Bow 1946) (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Knight, Lendall B. (Bow 1941) (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Knox, C. A. (Bow 1931) (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Kyle, Kim (Bow 1947) (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Lackey, William S. (Bow 1937) (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - LaFond, Paul D. (Bow 1943) (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Lamport, Richard M. (Bow 1942) (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Lancaster, Edgar W. (Bow 1930) (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Lane, David A. (Bow ?) (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Lang, Harold B. (Bow 1936) (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Lang, Raymond (Bow 1919) (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Laudley, Paul Jr. (Bow 1936) (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Leavitt, Brooks R. (Bow 1946) (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Leclair, Gustav O. (Bow 1936) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Lee, Alfred P. (Bow 1943) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Lee, Richard A. (Bow 1924) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Leete, Henry W. (Bow ch 1946) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Legate, Boyd O. (Bow 1940) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Lehrman, Harold (1939) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Lehrman, Melvin L. (Bow 1945) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Lengsfield, Byron H. (Bow 1945) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Leo, Stephen F. (Bow 1932) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Le Royer, Maxine F. (Bow 1941) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Levin, Jesse H. (Bow 1939) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Levin, Robert D. (Bow 1945) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Levin, Wilfred R. (Bow 1944) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Levine, Irving (Bow ch 1946) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Lewis, Eben H. (Bow 1941) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Lewis, Norval B. (Bow 1945) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Lewis, Richard H. (Bow 1945) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Lewis, Richard W. (Bow 1946) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Leydon, Theodore C. (Bow 1941) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Lifshitz, Shepard (Bow 1947) (Box 6, Folder 19a)
  - Lincoln, Edwin H. (Bow 1945) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Linehan, Thomas U. (Bow 1940) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Little, Clifford C. (Bow 1946) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Livingston, Robert M. (Bow 1944) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Loane, Ernest W. (Bow 1939) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Locke, Sherman (Bow 1942) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Loeman, Walter C. (Bow 1941) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Logan, Alan L. (Bow 1942) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Lombard, Reginald T. (Bow 1919) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Long, Albert S. (Bow 1944) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Lord, Frank D. (Bow 1938) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Lord, George M. (Bow 1943) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Lord, Hartley (Bow 1936) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Love, Robert B. (Bow 1923) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Lowell, William H. (Bow 1933) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Lowry, W. Kenneth (Fac) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Luce, Walter M. (Bow 1935) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Lunt, Robert H. (Bow 1942) (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - MacCarey, John C. (Bow 1939) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - MacGregor, A. B. (Bow 1945) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Mack, Thomas H. (Bow 1936) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - MacNaughton, James (Bow 1945) (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Macomber, David H. (Bow 1939) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Magee, John F. (Bow 1947) (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Main, W. L. (Bow 1944) (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Mallory, William W. (Bow 1941) (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Mansfield, William L. (Bow ch 1920) (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Marchildon, R. T. (Bow 1943) (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Marr, R. J. (Bow 1943) (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Marsh, H. Newman Jr. (Bow 1945) (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Marshall, Joel Y. (Bow 1934) (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Marston, Coburn (Bow 1942) (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Marston, Edward R. (Bow 1942) (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Martin, William H. (Bow 1943) (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Mason, Richard P. (Bow 1942) (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Mathers, Cortland (Bow 1946) (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Mathews, Curtice L. (Bow ch 1946) (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Maver, Quentin M. (Bow ch 1942) (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Maxwell, R. W. (Bow 1943) (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - May, Richard T. (Bow 1937) (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - McCarty, Robert L. (Bow 1941) (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - McClelland, Frank (Bow 1943) (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - McDuff, Omar R. (Bow 1941) (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - McKay, John S. (Bow 1942) (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - McKay Joseph, H. (Bow 1942) (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - McKenney, Fred R. (Bow 1939) (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - McKeown, William T. (Bow 1943) (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - McKown, Selden E. (Bow 1932) (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - McNeally, Douglass H. (Bow 1946) (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - McNeally, Eugene W. (Bow 1913) (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - McNiven, Roy W. (Bow 1941) (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - McPartland, Justin S. (Bow 1920) (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - McPharlin, Michael G. H. (Bow 1935) (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Medekin, Thomas K. (Bow 1946) (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Mergendahl, Charles H. (Bow 1941) (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Merriam, Donald E. (Bow 1931) (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Merrill, Arthur S. (Bow 1914) (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Merrill, Stephen E. (Bow 1935) (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Merrow, Clinton F. (Bow 1941) (Box 6, Folder 77a)
  - Michaud, Robert E. (Bow 1936) (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Michel, Jean-Claude D. (Bow 1943) (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Mick, C. Stetson (Bow 1945) (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Miller, August C. (Bow 1927) (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Mills, Amos S. (Bow 1937) (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Minderbender, Milo M. (Bow 1939) (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Mitchell, Allan W. (Bow 1935) (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Mitchell, Burroughs (Bow 1936) (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Mitchell, William (Bow 1940) (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Monahan, Paul W. (Bow 1945) (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Montgomery, David K. (Bow 1927) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Moody, William M. (Bow 1946) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Moore, Roswell (Bow 1927) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Moore, W. F. (Bow 1943) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Moran, Paul W. (Bow 1947) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Morgan, W. S. (Bow 1945) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Morrell, Paul P. (Bow 1945) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Morris, John (Bow 1934) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Morrison, George E. (Bow 1944) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Morse, Donald (1941) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Morse, Edward H. (Bow 1933) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Morse, Mayland H. (Bow 1942) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Morse, Robert W. (Bow 1943) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Morss, Robert D. (Bow 1910) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Moulton, Willis B. (Bow 1941) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Mudge, William (Bow ch 1944) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Muller, George M. (Bow 1944) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Muir, William M. (Bow 1944) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Munro, Hugh (Bow 1941) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Murdoch, Converse (Bow 1941) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Murdy, F. R. (Bow 1942) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Murray, Paul (Bow 1932) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Myrvaagnes, Kaspar O. (Bow 1931) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Nason, Richard B. (Bow 1935) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Nevels, Luman N. (Bow 1946) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Neverdouski, Thomas B. (Bow 1942) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Nichols, John D. (Bow 1939) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Niven, Paul K. Jr. (Bow 1946) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Novello, Russell (Bow 1940) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Noyes, Theodor A. (Bow 1944) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - O'Brien, Thomas L. (Bow 1936) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - O'Connor, D. Stanislaus (Bow 1918) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - O'Donnell, John H. (Bow 1937) (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Olds, C. A. (Bow 1946) (Box 7, Folder 34)